I always felt like having insurance was
important I just didn't realize the
value of it until this unfortunate
situation happened with us my cousin
fell ill and passed away and she was
like my little sister she's a pretty
smart cookie so she knew what insurance
was right for her and I was put in the
position where I had to take care of her
daughter Manulife took the financial
burden of taking care of her home had
she not had the mortgage protection
insurance it would have been very hard
for us to move forward and knowing that
I wouldn't have to worry about paying
for that mortgage was a huge sigh of
relief for us you know what they
promised is what we got the minute that
I made the phone call to the minute
things were paid oh I don't even think
it was a month it's made me think about
my own future making sure I've got the
right things in place for my own kids
when you're getting into buying a home
and getting your mortgage it's nice to
be informed and know what your options
are but I think it's really important as
a broker to let your clients know that
there's this added coverage and there is
value because trust me thank God we have
it
[Music]